<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Two Pointers on Forz Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/two-pointers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Two Pointers on Forz Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:41:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/two-pointers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>找到被指的新类型字符</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%89%BE%E5%88%B0%E8%A2%AB%E6%8C%87%E7%9A%84%E6%96%B0%E7%B1%BB%E5%9E%8B%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%89%BE%E5%88%B0%E8%A2%AB%E6%8C%87%E7%9A%84%E6%96%B0%E7%B1%BB%E5%9E%8B%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6/</guid>
      <description>题目: 新类型字符的定义如下： 新类型字符是长度为1或者2的字符串。 表现形式可以仅是小写字母,例如”e&amp;rdquo;;也可以是大写字母+小写字母</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>最长子串/子序列</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%9C%80%E9%95%BF%E5%AD%90%E4%B8%B2%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%9C%80%E9%95%BF%E5%AD%90%E4%B8%B2%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 392. Is Subsequence Given a string s and a string t, check if s is subsequence of t. You may assume that there is only lower case English letters in both s and t. t is potentially a very long (length ~= 500,000) string, and s is a short string (&amp;lt;=100). A subsequence of a string is a new string which is formed from the original string by deleting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>判断回文串</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%9B%9E%E6%96%87%E4%B8%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%9B%9E%E6%96%87%E4%B8%B2/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 9. Palindrome Number Determine whether an integer is a palindrome. Do this without extra space. Some hints: Could negative integers be palindromes? (ie, -1) If you are thinking of converting the integer to string, note the restriction of using extra space. You could also try reversing an integer. However, if you have solved the problem “Reverse Intege</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>在单链表中删除倒数第N个节点</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%9C%A8%E5%8D%95%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E4%B8%AD%E5%88%A0%E9%99%A4%E5%80%92%E6%95%B0%E7%AC%ACn%E4%B8%AA%E8%8A%82%E7%82%B9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%9C%A8%E5%8D%95%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E4%B8%AD%E5%88%A0%E9%99%A4%E5%80%92%E6%95%B0%E7%AC%ACn%E4%B8%AA%E8%8A%82%E7%82%B9/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 19. Remove Nth Node From End of List Given a linked list, remove the nth node from the end of list and return its head. For example, Given linked list: 1-&amp;gt;2-&amp;gt;3-&amp;gt;4-&amp;gt;5, and n = 2. After removing the second node from the end, the linked list becomes 1-&amp;gt;2-&amp;gt;3-&amp;gt;5. Note: Given n will always be valid. Try to do this in one pass. 解析： 根据题意</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>链表有环和相交问题</title>
      <link>/post/%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E6%9C%89%E7%8E%AF%E5%92%8C%E7%9B%B8%E4%BA%A4%E9%97%AE%E9%A2%98/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E6%9C%89%E7%8E%AF%E5%92%8C%E7%9B%B8%E4%BA%A4%E9%97%AE%E9%A2%98/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 141. Linked List Cycle Given a linked list, determine if it has a cycle in it. Follow up: Can you solve it without using extra space? 解析： FLOYD判圈算法(判断是否有环): 如何检测一个链表是否有环，如果有，那么如何确</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>删除有序数组/链表的重复值</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%88%A0%E9%99%A4%E6%9C%89%E5%BA%8F%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E5%80%BC/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 23:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%88%A0%E9%99%A4%E6%9C%89%E5%BA%8F%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E5%80%BC/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 26. Remove Duplicates from Sorted Array Given a sorted array, remove the duplicates in place such that each element appear only once and return the new length. Do not allocate extra space for another array, you must do this in place with constant memory. For example, Given input array nums = [1,1,2], Your function should return length = 2, with the first two elements of nums being 1 and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>容器的盛水量</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%AE%B9%E5%99%A8%E7%9A%84%E7%9B%9B%E6%B0%B4%E9%87%8F/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 23:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%AE%B9%E5%99%A8%E7%9A%84%E7%9B%9B%E6%B0%B4%E9%87%8F/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 11. Container With Most Water Given n non-negative integers a1, a2, …, an, where each represents a point at coordinate (i, ai). n vertical lines are drawn such that the two endpoints of line i is at (i, ai) and (i, 0). Find two lines, which together with x-axis forms a container, such that the container contains the most water. Note: You may not slant the container and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>判断变形字符串</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%8F%98%E5%BD%A2%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 22:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%8F%98%E5%BD%A2%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 383. Ransom Note Given an arbitrary ransom note string and another string containing letters from all the magazines, write a function that will return true if the ransom note can be constructed from the magazines ; otherwise, it will return false. Each letter in the magazine string can only be used once in your ransom note. Note: You may assume that both strings contain only lowercase letters. 1 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>划分数组/链表</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%88%92%E5%88%86%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%88%92%E5%88%86%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E9%93%BE%E8%A1%A8/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 75. Sort Colors Given an array with n objects colored red, white or blue, sort them so that objects of the same color are adjacent, with the colors in the order red, white and blue. Here, we will use the integers 0, 1, and 2 to represent the color red, white, and blue respectively. Note: You are not suppose to use the library</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>