<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hash on Forz Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/hash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hash on Forz Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 22:45:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/hash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>求两个数组的交集</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%B1%82%E4%B8%A4%E4%B8%AA%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%A4%E9%9B%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 22:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%B1%82%E4%B8%A4%E4%B8%AA%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%A4%E9%9B%86/</guid>
      <description>有序数组 以下两种方法都可以适用于数组中数据重复的情况。 长度相似 采用二路归并法来进行求解交集 对于数组A,B分别以i,j从头遍历数组。如果当前位</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>字符数组中的单独字符</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E5%8D%95%E7%8B%AC%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 23:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E5%8D%95%E7%8B%AC%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6/</guid>
      <description>判断字符数组中是否所有的字符都只出现过一次 题目: 给定一个字符类型数组chas[]，判断chas中是否所有的字符都只出现过一次,在保证额外空间</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>查找数组中的重复项</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%9F%A5%E6%89%BE%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E9%A1%B9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 23:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%9F%A5%E6%89%BE%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E9%A1%B9/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 217. Contains Duplicate Given an array of integers, find if the array contains any duplicates. Your function should return true if any value appears at least twice in the array, and it should return false if every element is distinct. 解析：直接构建哈希表 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 class Solution { public: bool containsDuplicate(vector&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;&amp;amp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>判断变形字符串</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%8F%98%E5%BD%A2%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 22:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%88%A4%E6%96%AD%E5%8F%98%E5%BD%A2%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 383. Ransom Note Given an arbitrary ransom note string and another string containing letters from all the magazines, write a function that will return true if the ransom note can be constructed from the magazines ; otherwise, it will return false. Each letter in the magazine string can only be used once in your ransom note. Note: You may assume that both strings contain only lowercase letters. canConstruct(&amp;quot;a&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;b&amp;quot;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>字符串A编辑成字符串B</title>
      <link>/post/%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2a%E7%BC%96%E8%BE%91%E6%88%90%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2a%E7%BC%96%E8%BE%91%E6%88%90%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2b/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 115. Distinct Subsequences Given a string S and a string T, count the number of distinct subsequences of T in S. A subsequence of a string is a new string which is formed from the original string by deleting some (can be none) of the characters without disturbing the relative positions of the remaining characters. (ie, “ACE” is a subsequence of “ABC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>最长上升子序列</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%9C%80%E9%95%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%8D%87%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%9C%80%E9%95%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%8D%87%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 300. Longest Increasing Subsequence Given an unsorted array of integers, find the length of longest increasing subsequence. For example, Given [10, 9, 2, 5, 3, 7, 101, 18], The longest increasing subsequence is [2, 3, 7, 101], therefore the length is 4. Note that there may be more than one LIS combination, it is only necessary for you to return the length. Your algorithm should run in O(n2) complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>重复的DNA子序列</title>
      <link>/post/%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E7%9A%84dna%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 19:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E9%87%8D%E5%A4%8D%E7%9A%84dna%E5%AD%90%E5%BA%8F%E5%88%97/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 187. Repeated DNA Sequences All DNA is composed of a series of nucleotides abbreviated as A, C, G, and T, for example: “ACGAATTCCG”. When studying DNA, it is sometimes useful to identify repeated sequences within the DNA. Write a function to find all the 10-letter-long sequences (substrings) that occur more than once in a DNA molecule. For</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>同构字符串</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%90%8C%E6%9E%84%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 19:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%90%8C%E6%9E%84%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 205. Isomorphic Strings Given two strings s and t, determine if they are isomorphic. Two strings are isomorphic if the characters in s can be replaced to get t. All occurrences of a character must be replaced with another character while preserving the order of characters. No two characters may map to the same character but a character may map to itself. For example, Given “egg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>设计RandomPool结构</title>
      <link>/post/%E8%AE%BE%E8%AE%A1randompool%E7%BB%93%E6%9E%84/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 19:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E8%AE%BE%E8%AE%A1randompool%E7%BB%93%E6%9E%84/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 380. Insert Delete GetRandom O(1) Design a data structure that supports all following operations in average O(1) time. insert(val): Inserts an item val to the set if not already present. remove(val): Removes an item val from the set if present. getRandom: Returns a random element from current set of elements. Each element must have the same probability of being returned. Example: 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulls and Cows</title>
      <link>/post/bulls-and-cows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 16:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bulls-and-cows/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 299. Bulls and Cows You are playing the following Bulls and Cows game with your friend: You write down a number and ask your friend to guess what the number is. Each time your friend makes a guess, you provide a hint that indicates how many digits in said guess match your secret number exactly in both digit and position (called “bulls”)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>两个数组的相交数字</title>
      <link>/post/%E4%B8%A4%E4%B8%AA%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E7%9B%B8%E4%BA%A4%E6%95%B0%E5%AD%97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E4%B8%A4%E4%B8%AA%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E7%9B%B8%E4%BA%A4%E6%95%B0%E5%AD%97/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 349. Intersection of Two Arrays Given two arrays, write a function to compute their intersection. Example: Given nums1 = [1, 2, 2, 1], nums2 = [2, 2], return [2]. Note: Each element in the result must be unique. The result can be in any order. 解析： 因为要求结果元素不重复，所以采用unord</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
