<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>背包DP on Forz Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/%E8%83%8C%E5%8C%85dp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 背包DP on Forz Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/%E8%83%8C%E5%8C%85dp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>正整数数组的最小不可组成和</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%AD%A3%E6%95%B4%E6%95%B0%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E6%9C%80%E5%B0%8F%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AF%E7%BB%84%E6%88%90%E5%92%8C/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%AD%A3%E6%95%B4%E6%95%B0%E6%95%B0%E7%BB%84%E7%9A%84%E6%9C%80%E5%B0%8F%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AF%E7%BB%84%E6%88%90%E5%92%8C/</guid>
      <description>题目: 给定一个正数数组arr,其中所有的值都为整数，以下是最小不可组成和的概念： 把arr每个子集内的所有元素加起来会出现很多值，其中最小的记</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>组合</title>
      <link>/post/%E7%BB%84%E5%90%88/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E7%BB%84%E5%90%88/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 39. Combination Sum Given a set of candidate numbers (C) (without duplicates) and a target number (T), find all unique combinations in C where the candidate numbers sums to T. The same repeated number may be chosen from C unlimited number of times. Note: All numbers (including target) will be positive integers. The solution set must not contain duplicate combinations. For example, given candidate set [2, 3, 6, 7]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>字符串A编辑成字符串B</title>
      <link>/post/%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2a%E7%BC%96%E8%BE%91%E6%88%90%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2a%E7%BC%96%E8%BE%91%E6%88%90%E5%AD%97%E7%AC%A6%E4%B8%B2b/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 115. Distinct Subsequences Given a string S and a string T, count the number of distinct subsequences of T in S. A subsequence of a string is a new string which is formed from the original string by deleting some (can be none) of the characters without disturbing the relative positions of the remaining characters. (ie, “ACE” is a subsequence of “ABC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>子集</title>
      <link>/post/%E5%AD%90%E9%9B%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E5%AD%90%E9%9B%86/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 78. Subsets Given a set of distinct integers, nums, return all possible subsets. Note: The solution set must not contain duplicate subsets. For example, If nums = [1,2,3], a solution is: [ [3], [1], [2], [1,2,3], [1,3], [2,3], [1,2], [] ] 解析：要求输出所有子集，且输出有序，而每个元素只有出现和</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>换钱</title>
      <link>/post/%E6%8D%A2%E9%92%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 16:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%E6%8D%A2%E9%92%B1/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode 322. Coin Change You are given coins of different denominations and a total amount of money amount. Write a function to compute the fewest number of coins that you need to make up that amount. If that amount of money cannot be made up by any combination of the coins, return -1. Example 1: coins = [1, 2, 5], amount = 11 return 3 (11 = 5 + 5</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
